// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which built-in method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
    answer: "push()",
    options: [
      "last()",
      "put()",
      "push()",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
    answer: "reverse()",
    options: [
      "changeOrder(order)",
      "sort(order)",
      "split()",
      "reverse()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following function of String object combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
    answer: "concat()",
    options: [
      "sum()",
      "concat()",
      "merge()",
      "append()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A Function Associated With An object is Called:",
    answer: "method",
    options: [
      "function",
      "method",
      "link",
      "element"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "GetMonth() returns The Month as:",
    answer: "Int",
    options: [
      "String",
      "Char",
      "Float",
      "Int"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who created JavaScript",
    answer: "Brendan Eich",
    options: [
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "Bjarne Stroustrup",
      "Brendan Eich",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How long did Brendan Eich take to write the JavaScript programming language?",
    answer: "10 days",
    options: [
      "5 weeks",
      "2 months",
      "10 months",
      "10 days"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is not a reserved word in JavaScript?",
    answer: "undefined",
    options: [
      "undefined",
      "finally",
      "throw",
      "default"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display “Fullstack Academy” in an alert box using JavaScript?",
    answer: "alert('Fullstack Academy')",
    options: [
      "msg('Fullstack Academy')",
      "alertbox('Fullstack Academy')",
      "alert('Fullstack Academy')",
      "msgbox('Fullstack Academy')"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for adding comments in JavaScript?",
    answer: "//This is a comment",
    options: [
      "**This is a comment**",
      "//This is a comment",
      "#This is a comment#",
      "$This is a comment$"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is the JavaScript syntax for printing values in Console?",
    answer: "console.log(5)",
    options: [
      "console.print(5)",
      "print.console(5)",
      "print(5)",
      "console.log(5)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the method in JavaScript used to remove the whitespace at the beginning and end of any string?",
    answer: "trim()",
    options: [
      "strip() ",
      "trim()",
      "stripped()",
      "trimmed()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which was the first browser to support JavaScript?",
    answer: "Netscape",
    options: [
      "Mozilla Firefox",
      "Google Chrome",
      "Netscape",
      "IE"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the following is not the JavaScript operator?",
    answer: "this",
    options: [
      "this",
      "typeof",
      "delete",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is not a mouse event?",
    answer: "onmousescroller",
    options: [
      "onclick",
      "onmouseover",
      "onmousemove",
      "onmousescroller"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "What was JavaScript's original name?",
    answer: "Mocha",
    options: [
      "Mocha",
      "LiveScript",
      "Escript",
      "Javascript"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What are the types of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Prompt",
      "Alert",
      "Confirm",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which one is Ternary Operator",
    answer: "?:",
    options: [
      ">?",
      "?#",
      "?*",
      "?:"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "How do you round the number 1.25 to the nearest integer?",
    answer: "Math.round(1.25)",
    options: [
      "round(1.25)",
      "Math.round(1.25)",
      "Math.floor(1.25)",
      "round(1.25)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which event is specific to the keyboard",
    answer: "onkeydown",
    options: [
      "onclick",
      "onfocus",
      "onkeyboardpress",
      "onkeydown"
    ]
  },
];

